♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 37=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 37 =
Hey.
يا.
If Fu Rong knows
إذا كان فو رونغ يعرف
that there's no copy in the flash disk,
أنه لا يوجد نسخة في قرص الفلاش ،
what will she think?
ماذا ستفكر؟
She has done so many awful things.
لقد فعلت الكثير من الأشياء الفظيعة.
The police took her away.
أخذتها الشرطة بعيدا.
This is what she deserves.
هذا ما تستحقه.
Well...
نحن سوف...
Grandpa must be very sad
يجب أن يكون الجد حزينًا جدًا
right now.
فى الحال.
Then why don't we do something
إذن لماذا لا نفعل شيئًا
that can make him happy?
يمكن أن يجعله سعيدا؟
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.
Will you marry me?
هل ستتزوجني؟
Perfect.
في احسن الاحوال.
Captivating.
آسر.
Beautiful.
جميلة.
Mom.
أم.
Why do you smile like that?
لماذا تبتسم هكذا؟
My daughter is finally getting married.
ابنتي تتزوج أخيرًا.
At last.
أخيرا.
Everyone else cries when the daughter gets married.
الجميع يبكي عندما تتزوج الابنة.
Only you would look so happy.
أنت فقط ستبدو سعيدًا جدًا.
Of course I'm happy.
بالطبع أنا سعيد.
What if Fu Sihan bullies me?
ماذا لو كان فو سيهان يتنمر علي؟
Only you would bully him.
أنت فقط سوف تتنمر عليه.
My little girl.
ابنتي الصغيرة.
Why do you take his side, mom?
لماذا تأخذ جانبه يا أمي؟
He's not your child.
إنه ليس طفلك.
I am.
انا.
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
Sihan.
سيهان.
Grandpa.
الجد.
If your dad
إذا كان والدك
could live to this day and see this,
يمكن أن يعيش حتى يومنا هذا ويرى هذا ،
how nice would that be?
كم سيكون ذلك لطيفا؟
Now grandpa wants you two
الآن جدي يريدكما اثنان
to give me a great-grandson
ليعطيني ابن حفيد
in the summer.
في الصيف.
This is your mission.
هذه هي مهمتك.
Grandpa.
الجد.
There's so little time.
هناك القليل من الوقت.
I'm afraid we won't make it.
أخشى أننا لن نفعل ذلك.
You have to.
عليك أن.
Yes, grandpa.
نعم جدي.
You have my word.
اعدك.